George Lloyd-Anderson | Computer Science Masters Graduate

Location: Leeds/Wakefield Telephone: 07720 997840

Email: georgewlloydanderson@gmail.com

Professional Profile

Computer Science Masters Graduate, specializing in Android development with projects ranging from an eHealth eating disorder monitor for use within clinical CBT treatments to a smart-tech-enabled fitness app for dogs. Actively involved within charity work having run two fundraising societies at Leeds Beckett and volunteering for Guide Dogs. Awarded with the Leeds Beckett Gold Award and the prestigious, National Student Fundraiser of the Year award for dedicating over 300 hours in 2018/19 to charitable causes.

Education & Qualifications

Leeds Beckett University - Dates attended (2015 - 2020)

Computer Science - MENG (1st Predicted)

Modules studied include, Networking, Cloud Computing, Advanced Software Engineering, Android App Development, and Intelligent Systems with languages used including Java, C#, PHP, and assembly. Noteworthy Projects include:

- Master's Dissertation: A native Material Design based Android Application for the self-monitoring of eating disorders in CBT based treatments.
- **Group Dissertation:** Dog fitness application, interacting with Fitbark via the Fitbit API. Personally, responsible for the design and development of apps front-end.
- Command Parser: Java GUI Application teaching users about programming with a custom language featuring commands, methods, and loops.
- **Turtle Game:** Java-based turtle game allowing the user to enter commands to navigate a sprite around the screen drawing lines behind it.

Outwood Grange Academy Sixth Form – Dates attended (2012 – 2015)

- A-Level ICT B
- A-Level Business Studies D
- AS Sociology C
- AS Media Studies C
- AS Extended Project B

Experience:

Society President / Campaign Leader (February 2018 – March 2020)

Leeds Beckett Students Union - Leeds

- Founded a mental health campaign, designing both a website and flyer reaching over 1000 students, and encouraging changes to the Unions webpage.
- Successfully managed two fundraising societies, raising awareness and money for charitable causes with over 40 members and multiple charity partnerships.
- Represented the University at two National Student Fundraising Conferences, earning national recognition for work with student fundraising.

 Worked with charity partners to organize local street clutter campaign, gaining recognition from local MP.

Summer Software Development Internship (July 2019 - September 2019)

Target Information Systems - Barnsley

- Worked with HTML5, SASS, PHP and Bootstrap to customize an existing project to meet client specifications.
- Successfully undertook both guided and independent learning in Web Design, working with other developers to grow my skills.

Volunteer Fundraiser (July 2018 - Present)

Guide Dogs - Leeds

- Worked as part of a team to raise thousands of pounds over several events.
- Communicated the aims of the charity to both adults and children.
- Encouraged engagement with charity platforms and opportunities.

Awards and Recognition

- > National Student Fundraiser of the Year 2019 (NSFA)
- Leeds Beckett Award Gold (Leeds Beckett)
- Diamond Volunteering Award (Leeds Beckett Students Union)

Interests

Interests: App Development, Gaming, Volunteering, Craft and Dogs